xboxisozone.com 2013-06-06

# Privacy Policy • The Iso Zone

**Simplified Version: Theisozone.com will never share your personal information with advertisers or spammers, period.**

Theisozone.com, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to our users' privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for www.Theisozone.com including the following:

What personally identifiable information Theisozone.com collects.  
What personally identifiable information third parties collect through this web site.  
What organization collects the information.  
How Theisozone.com uses the information.  
With whom Theisozone.com may share user information.  
What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.  
What type of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Theisozone.com's control.  
How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement, please send them to privacy@Theisozone.com.  

## What personally identifiable information Theisozone.com collects

Theisozone.com, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on Theisozone.com. Theisozone.com, Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our web site.

**Registration  
**In order to access the membership areas of this web site, a user must first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information including name and email address. We use this information to ensure account security and uniqueness and to contact a user in case a problem occurs. In addition, registered users must provide payment information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes only. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

## How Theisozone.com uses the information

**Profile  
**A profile is stored information that is kept on individual users that details their viewing preferences and is then used for marketing purposes. Theisozone.com does not use stored user settings for marketing purposes. User settings (default chart settings, favorite lists, etc.) are kept solely for the purpose of customizing our paying users' visits. We do not share your profile with other third parties.  
Cookies 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once you close your browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser's help file directions.

We use a session cookie to control access to our membership areas.

If you are a member and you have checked the "Log Me In Automatically" box on our home page, we store your user ID and password in persistent cookies so that you do not need to re-enter that information each time you visit the site.

If you reject the use of cookies, you will not be able to access the membership areas of Theisozone.com however you will still be able to use the web site minus the community features.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Third Party Advertisers**  
The ads appearing on this web site are delivered to the users by either AdBrite or Amazon, our web advertising partners. Information about the users' visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not personal information like user name and password) is used to serve ads to users on this site.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Theisozone.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any other advertisers.

**Log Files**  
Like most web sites, we use web server log files. Records in our log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service providers (ISP's), referring pages, exit pages, platform types, and date/time stamps. We use web server log files to administer the site, to provide broad traffic information for site planning purposes, and to ensure that our terms of service agreement is being adhered to. IP addresses are not tied to personally identifiable information in our web server log files.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Theisozone.com Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

## Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this web site and place a notice of such changes on our home page and other places we deem appropriate.

If we decide to start using users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users via email and/or by posting a notice on our web site for 30 days.  

## Contact Information 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us using our web-based feedback form or by sending email to support AT theisozone.com.

_Policy last updated June 1st 2012_
